couponcodes4u.com 2013-05-25

# Privacy Policy

  * Categories
    *  __Business & Home Office
    *  __Fashion
    *  __Finance & Insurance
    *  __Gifts & Occasions
    *  __Health & Beauty
    *  __Home & Garden
    *  __Kids, Babies & Toys
    *  __Misc.
    *  __Mobile, TV & Broadband
    *  __Motoring
    *  __Music, Books, Games & Movies
    *  __Online Services
    *  __Pets
    *  __Sports, Fitness & Outdoors
    *  __Technology & Electrical
    *  __Travel
  * Top 50
  *  __Exclusives __
  * Printable Coupons
  * Grocery Coupons
  * Free Shipping
  * Tax Returns

CouponCodes4u.com knows that you may have concerns about your privacy while shopping or surfing on the Internet. Our Privacy Policy describes how we use and do not use information provided to us at CouponCodes4u.com , and the steps we take to protect it.

## Personal Information

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to CouponCodes4u.com . You are free to fully use CouponCodes4u.com anonymously. When contacting us or submitting feedback, you are welcome to give your personal information or to remain anonymous. We intend to protect the quality and integrity of any of your personally identifiable information that you do provide us. The feedback form automatically captures your IP address and browser version information. This information is used to aid us in fixing problems and to serve you better. This same information is automatically recorded in our server log files as pages, images, etc. are requested, as part of a standard web-server setup.

## Business Relationships

This site contains links to other websites. CouponCodes4u.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

## Cookies

This site uses cookies to control popup windows and advertisements. The main purpose of these cookies isto limit the number of advertisements you are presented with on a given visit to the site.

## Mailing List

If you join our mailing list, we will keep your email address and any demographics information you volunteer strictly confidential. We will never give or sell your email address or any information about you to anyone else.
